{
    "studyset": "22676482", 
    "data": [
        {
            "question": "time",
            "answer": "shí jiān"
        },
        {
            "question": "year",
            "answer": "nián"
        },
        {
            "question": "people",
            "answer": "rén"
        },
        {
            "question": "way",
            "answer": "fāng shì"
        },
        {
            "question": "day",
            "answer": "rì"
        },
        {
            "question": "man",
            "answer": "nán rén"
        },
        {
            "question": "thing",
            "answer": "shì"
        },
        {
            "question": "woman",
            "answer": "nǚ rén"
        },
        {
            "question": "life",
            "answer": "shēng huó"
        },
        {
            "question": "child",
            "answer": "ér tóng"
        },
        {
            "question": "world",
            "answer": "shì jiè"
        },
        {
            "question": "school",
            "answer": "xué xiào"
        },
        {
            "question": "state",
            "answer": "zhèng fǔ"
        },
        {
            "question": "family",
            "answer": "jiā tíng"
        },
        {
            "question": "student",
            "answer": "xué shēng"
        },
        {
            "question": "group",
            "answer": "zǔ zhī"
        },
        {
            "question": "country",
            "answer": "guó jiā"
        },
        {
            "question": "problem",
            "answer": "wèn tí"
        },
        {
            "question": "hand",
            "answer": "shǒu"
        },
        {
            "question": "part",
            "answer": "bù fèn"
        },
        {
            "question": "place",
            "answer": "dì fāng"
        },
        {
            "question": "case",
            "answer": "àn"
        },
        {
            "question": "week",
            "answer": "xīng qī"
        },
        {
            "question": "company",
            "answer": "gōng sī"
        },
        {
            "question": "system",
            "answer": "xì tǒng"
        },
        {
            "question": "program",
            "answer": "chéng xu"
        },
        {
            "question": "question",
            "answer": "wèn tí"
        },
        {
            "question": "work",
            "answer": "gōng zuò"
        },
        {
            "question": "government",
            "answer": "zhèng fǔ"
        },
        {
            "question": "number",
            "answer": "shù zì"
        },
        {
            "question": "night",
            "answer": "yè"
        },
        {
            "question": "point",
            "answer": "diǎn"
        },
        {
            "question": "home",
            "answer": "jiā"
        },
        {
            "question": "water",
            "answer": "shuǐ"
        },
        {
            "question": "room",
            "answer": "fáng jiān"
        },
        {
            "question": "mother",
            "answer": "mǔ qīn"
        },
        {
            "question": "area",
            "answer": "qū yù"
        },
        {
            "question": "money",
            "answer": "qián"
        },
        {
            "question": "story",
            "answer": "gù shi"
        },
        {
            "question": "fact",
            "answer": "shí shì"
        },
        {
            "question": "month",
            "answer": "yuè"
        },
        {
            "question": "lot",
            "answer": "hěn duō"
        },
        {
            "question": "right",
            "answer": "duì"
        },
        {
            "question": "study",
            "answer": "xué xí"
        },
        {
            "question": "book",
            "answer": "shū"
        },
        {
            "question": "eye",
            "answer": "yǎn jīng"
        },
        {
            "question": "job",
            "answer": "gōng zuò"
        },
        {
            "question": "word",
            "answer": "cí"
        },
        {
            "question": "business",
            "answer": "shāng yè"
        },
        {
            "question": "issue",
            "answer": "wèn tí"
        },
        {
            "question": "side",
            "answer": "biān"
        },
        {
            "question": "kind",
            "answer": "zhǒng lèi"
        },
        {
            "question": "head",
            "answer": "tóu"
        },
        {
            "question": "house",
            "answer": "fáng zi"
        },
        {
            "question": "service",
            "answer": "fú wù"
        },
        {
            "question": "friend",
            "answer": "péng yǒu"
        },
        {
            "question": "father",
            "answer": "fù qīn"
        },
        {
            "question": "power",
            "answer": "lì"
        },
        {
            "question": "hour",
            "answer": "xiǎo shí"
        },
        {
            "question": "game",
            "answer": "yóu xì"
        },
        {
            "question": "line",
            "answer": "xiàn"
        },
        {
            "question": "end",
            "answer": "jié shù"
        },
        {
            "question": "member",
            "answer": "chéng yuán"
        },
        {
            "question": "law",
            "answer": "fǎ lǜ"
        },
        {
            "question": "car",
            "answer": "qì chē"
        },
        {
            "question": "city",
            "answer": "chéng shì"
        },
        {
            "question": "community",
            "answer": "shè qū"
        },
        {
            "question": "name",
            "answer": "míng zì"
        },
        {
            "question": "president",
            "answer": "zǒng tǒng"
        },
        {
            "question": "team",
            "answer": "duì wǔ"
        },
        {
            "question": "minute",
            "answer": "fēn zhōng"
        },
        {
            "question": "idea",
            "answer": "gè diǎn"
        },
        {
            "question": "kid",
            "answer": "hái zi"
        },
        {
            "question": "body",
            "answer": "shēn tǐ"
        },
        {
            "question": "information",
            "answer": "xìn xī"
        },
        {
            "question": "back",
            "answer": "bèi hòu"
        },
        {
            "question": "parent",
            "answer": "fù mǔ"
        },
        {
            "question": "face",
            "answer": "liǎn"
        },
        {
            "question": "others",
            "answer": "qí tā rén"
        },
        {
            "question": "level",
            "answer": "chéng dù"
        },
        {
            "question": "office",
            "answer": "bàn gōng shì"
        },
        {
            "question": "door",
            "answer": "mén"
        },
        {
            "question": "health",
            "answer": "jiàn kāng"
        },
        {
            "question": "person",
            "answer": "rén"
        },
        {
            "question": "art",
            "answer": "yì shù"
        },
        {
            "question": "war",
            "answer": "zhàn zhēng"
        },
        {
            "question": "history",
            "answer": "lì shǐ"
        },
        {
            "question": "party",
            "answer": "dǎng pái"
        },
        {
            "question": "result",
            "answer": "jié guǒ"
        },
        {
            "question": "change",
            "answer": "biàn"
        },
        {
            "question": "morning",
            "answer": "zǎo shàng"
        },
        {
            "question": "reason",
            "answer": "yuán yīn"
        },
        {
            "question": "research",
            "answer": "yán jiū"
        },
        {
            "question": "girl",
            "answer": "nǚ hái"
        },
        {
            "question": "guy",
            "answer": "nán hái"
        },
        {
            "question": "moment",
            "answer": "shùn jiān"
        },
        {
            "question": "air",
            "answer": "kōng qì"
        },
        {
            "question": "teacher",
            "answer": "lǎo shī"
        },
        {
            "question": "force",
            "answer": "lì"
        },
        {
            "question": "education",
            "answer": "jiào yù"
        }
    ]
}